Welcome! After some hard work, now our climbing to top is finally working.
欢迎！欢迎 经过一些艰苦的工作，现在我们的攀登到顶部终于可以工作了。
And with the ability to climb up to the ledge now, our climbing system is really coming together.
随着现在能够爬到壁架上，我们的攀登系统真正地形成了。
And the next thing that I want to add in is,
而接下来我想加进去的是、
see now we are already at the top of a mesh, and by pressing the same climb action key,
现在我们已经在网状结构的顶部了，通过按同样的爬升动作键、
wouldn't it be nice if we can climb down the ledge?
如果我们能爬下壁架，那不是很好吗？
If we can do that, it can make our climbing system so much better.
如果我们能做到这一点，就能使我们的攀登系统变得更好。
And to achieve what we want, same as every other feature that we've created so far,
为了达到我们的目的，就像我们到目前为止所创建的其他功能一样、
we'll first need to do some kind of check and climb down.
我们首先需要做一些检查并爬下来。
And with everything that we've done so far, I think this will be a perfect challenge for you to implement by yourself.
鉴于我们到目前为止所做的一切，我认为这将是一个完美的挑战，让你自己来实现。
So what we want here is simple, when this climb action key is pressed, we want to climb down the ledge if we can.
所以我们在这里想要的很简单，当这个爬升动作键被按下时，如果可以的话，我们想爬下壁架。
So checking the condition will be our first step, and I'm going to give you a few examples.
所以检查条件将是我们的第一步，我将给你几个例子。
You can decide how you want to implement the check.
你可以决定你想如何实现检查。
In the scenario one, by pressing the climb action key, we should be able to climb down.
在场景一中，通过按爬升动作键，我们应该能够爬下来。
But in the scenario two and three, we shouldn't be able to do so.
但是在情景二和情景三中，我们不应该能够这样做。
So the key here is to rule out these two situations.
所以这里的关键是要排除这两种情况。
Feel free to use any methods that you see fit.
请随意使用你认为合适的任何方法。
And same as always, if the condition is true, I'd like you to print a message to the screen to say "can climb down".
和以往一样，如果条件为真，我希望你在屏幕上打印一条信息，说 "可以爬下来"。
Alright, put the video now and give this a go and I'll see you in the solution video.
好了，现在把视频放上去，给它一个机会，我们在解决视频中见。
[Music]
[音乐]